seoforgoogle.com 2010-09-02

# Privacy Policy - SEOforGoogle

**SEOforGoogle's Online Privacy Policy**  
---  
SEOforGoogle recognizes and shares the privacy concerns of visitors to our Web site. SEOforGoogle's On-Line Privacy Policy informs Web site visitors about 1) what we collect and its security 2) benefits to you of what we collect and how we use the information, and 3) the choice you have about SEOforGoogle’s use of the information.  
**About Me -**  
**What personal information does SEOforGoogle collect about me?**  
Visitors to SEOforGoogle's Web site browse the site anonymously. Visitors are not required to provide any personal information to SEOforGoogle in order to access our Web site.   
It is not our practice to request personal information solely for marketing purposes.   
Like all websites, SEOforGoogle has the ability to track and store the referring website you visited before visiting SEOforGoogle’s website. We also gather statistical information concerning Web traffic and usage patterns. This enables SEOforGoogle to evaluate what our customer’s want, provide adequate capacity for our visitors, and display information in the best manner.  
**Choice -**  
**Does SEOforGoogle disclose collected information to third parties?**  
SEOforGoogle does not resell or transfer E-mail addresses or any other personal information to third parties engaged in e-commerce. It is not SEOforGoogle's practice to disclose personal information to third parties without your authorization.  
**Jurisdiction / Enforceability -**  
Use of this site shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Pennsylvania without giving effect to any principles of conflicts of laws. Any dispute concerning this site shall be subject to the exclusive venue of a court of competent jurisdiction. 

Should any provision of our terms and conditions be held invalid, unlawful or for any reason unenforceable, then the invalid, unlawful or unenforceable provision shall be severable from the remaining provisions. Such invalid, unlawful or unenforceable provision shall not affect the validity or enforceability of the remaining provisions.   
  
The information and descriptions contained in this site are intended as general information and are not necessarily complete descriptions of all terms, exclusions and conditions applicable to the products and services offered by SEOforGoogle
